This Christmas has me deeply reflecting on the authentic and true life of Jesus.
I'm Muslim, so I don't celebrate Christmas religiously.
But as the world tries to divide us, I want to highlight the things that make us have more in common, actually.
Because unity is power.
And Muslims love Jesus.
I don't know if you know this.
We love Jesus.
We call Jesus Sayyid Na'isa.
And the biggest difference between Islam and Christianity is that we don't believe Jesus is the Son of God, but we do believe he is the most important prophet.
He's actually mentioned more times in the Quran than Prophet Muhammad.
And we call him Sayyid Na'isa.
So anytime you meet someone named Isa, you'll be like, wow, you're named Jesus.
And yeah, I mean, this year, like, my heart is totally broken, along with a lot of us, like, mourning and fighting for the freedom of Palestine.
But also reflecting on the story of Sayyid Na'isa, Jesus, and, you know, being born, fleeing persecution, fleeing genocide.
At the same time seeing Palestinian children being pulled out of the rubble.
And even though I don't celebrate Christmas religiously, I really welcome this opportunity to reflect on Jesus and the messages and lessons that he brought.
Free Palestine.